<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Setting-up Cloud9 on AWS Quick Start Workshop</title>
    <link>https://vsnyc.github.io/forge-smartbuilding-workshop/30_setup_cloud9.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Setting-up Cloud9 on AWS Quick Start Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vsnyc.github.io/forge-smartbuilding-workshop/30_setup_cloud9/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fork Quick Start repo</title>
      <link>https://vsnyc.github.io/forge-smartbuilding-workshop/30_setup_cloud9/1_create_new_gitrepo.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vsnyc.github.io/forge-smartbuilding-workshop/30_setup_cloud9/1_create_new_gitrepo.html</guid>
      <description>You must have a GitHub account to fork an exisitng repo. If you do not have an account create one by following these instructions Signing up for a new GitHub Account   Make sure you are logged into your GitHub account  Each AWS Quick Start consists of a GitHub repo where all the contents of the Quick Start live.
For this workshop, you will create a fork of the Autodesk Forge repo in your own github account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start scaffolding</title>
      <link>https://vsnyc.github.io/forge-smartbuilding-workshop/30_setup_cloud9/20_create_scaffolding.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vsnyc.github.io/forge-smartbuilding-workshop/30_setup_cloud9/20_create_scaffolding.html</guid>
      <description>The GitHub repository for the Autodesk Forge Quick Start includes the following files and folders:
 .taskcat.yml - Contains the test configuration and parameters used for automated testing. templates - Contains the AWS CloudFormation templates for the Quick Start. The templates can be in .yaml or .json file formats. packages - Contains the Forge application that gets deployed as part of the Quick Start submodules - Used for any referenced Quick Starts that are configured as submodules of the Quick Start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using the Event Engine dashboard</title>
      <link>https://vsnyc.github.io/forge-smartbuilding-workshop/30_setup_cloud9/30_ee_dashboard.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vsnyc.github.io/forge-smartbuilding-workshop/30_setup_cloud9/30_ee_dashboard.html</guid>
      <description>In a browser, go to the Event Engine dashboard page. Enter the 12 digit hash provided to your team and choose Accept Terms &amp;amp; Login. ![arch]((https://vsnyc.github.io/forge-smartbuilding-workshop/images/ee-dashboard-login.png) One the next page, choose the option to sign in with your personal or corporate email address using a One-Time Password (OTP) ![arch]((https://vsnyc.github.io/forge-smartbuilding-workshop/images/ee-dashboard-otp-login.png?height=40%&amp;amp;width=40%) On the next page, provide your email address and choose Send passcode. ![arch]((https://vsnyc.github.io/forge-smartbuilding-workshop/images/receive-otp-email.png?height=40%&amp;amp;width=40%)
 On the next page, input the OTP you received via email and choose Sign in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Git CLI</title>
      <link>https://vsnyc.github.io/forge-smartbuilding-workshop/30_setup_cloud9/40_setup_github_cli.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vsnyc.github.io/forge-smartbuilding-workshop/30_setup_cloud9/40_setup_github_cli.html</guid>
      <description>Through out this workshop, you will run GitHub commands from your Cloud9 workspace terminal window, to perform different operations on your GitHub repo.
By default, Cloud9 workspace comes installed with Git CLI. However, you need to configure it to use with your GitHub account.
Configure Git Profile In your Cloud9 IDE, open a new terminal, run these two commands, one at a time, substituting your Git name and email address for USER_NAME and EMAIL_ADDRESS, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>